<song>
  <title>Father and Son (unedited)</title>
  <artist>Cat Stevens</artist>
  <tempo>76</tempo>
  <parts>
    <part>
      <type>Verse</type>
      <lyrics>
        <line>It's not time to make a change, just relax, take it easy. You're still young, that's your fault, there's so much you have to know.</line>
        <line>Find a girl, settle down, if you want you can marry. Look at me, I am old but I'm happy.</line>
        <line></line>
        <line>I was once like you are now and I know that it's not easy. To be calm when you've found something going on.</line>
        <line>But take your time, think a lot, think of everything you've got. For you will still be here tomorrow but your dreams may not.</line>
      </lyrics>
      <chords>
        <line>G D/F# C Am7 G Em Am Am7 D</line>
        <line>G D/F# C Am7 G Em Am Am7 D</line>
        <line></line>
        <line>G D C Am7 G Em Am Am7 D</line>
        <line>G D C Am7 G Em D G</line>
      </chords>
    </part>
    <part>
      <type>Verse</type>
      <lyrics>
        <line>Oh, how can I try to explain? 'Cause when I do he turns away again. It's always been the same, same old story.</line>
        <line>From the moment I could talk, I was ordered to listen. Now there's a way and I know that I have to go away.</line>
        <line>I know I have to go.</line>
      </lyrics>
      <chords>
        <line>G Bm C Am7 G Em Am7 D</line>
        <line>G Bm C Am7 G Em D G</line>
        <line>D C G</line>
      </chords>
    </part>
    <part>
      <type>Solo</type>
      <lyrics>
        <line></line>
      </lyrics>
      <chords>
        <line>G D C Am7 G Em Am Am7 D</line>
        <line>G D C Am7 G Em D G</line>
        <line>D C G C/G G C/G</line>
      </chords>
    </part>
    <part>
      <type>Verse</type>
      <lyrics>
        <line>It's not time to make a change, just sit down, take it slowly. You're still young, that's your fault, there's so much you have to go through</line>
        <line>Find a girl, settle down, if you want you can marry. Look at me, I am old but I am happy</line>
      </lyrics>
      <chords>
        <line>G D/F# C Am7 G Em Am Am7 D</line>
        <line>G D/F# C Am7 G Em Am Am7 D</line>
      </chords>
    </part>
    <part>
      <type>Verse</type>
      <lyrics>
        <line>All the times that I've cried, keepin' all the things I knew inside. It's hard but it's harder to ignore it</line>
        <line>If they were right I'd agree, but it's them they know, not me. Now there's a way and I know that I have to go away</line>
        <line>I know I have to go</line>
      </lyrics>
      <chords>
        <line>G Bm C Am7 G Em Am7 D</line>
        <line>G Bm C Am7 G Em D G</line>
        <line>D C G</line>
      </chords>
    </part>
  </parts>
</song>